{
    "question": "Jawaban soal vocabulary building kelas 11\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>halaman brp y??</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>........</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "i-admit-my-mistake-we-learn-a-lot-about-it-the-wind-blow-la-101",
            "question": "I (admit) my mistake    we (learn) a lot about it\r\nthe wind (blow) last night\r\nwe (meet) in prague\r\nwhen she heard it she (cry)\r\ni (put) the book on the desk\r\n\r\ncomplete the sentences with correct verbs, us simple past tense\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p><strong>???</strong></p><p>We <strong>learned</strong> a lot about it.</p><p>The wind <strong>blowed </strong>last night.</p><p>We <strong>met</strong> in the prague.</p><p>When she heard it she <strong>cried</strong>.</p><p><strong>???</strong></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf gua tdk tau untuk no. 1 sama 6</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "4-tito-is-in-the-library-his-hobby-is-a-singing-b-dancin-884",
            "question": "4. Tito is in the library. His hobby is ....    a, singing\r\nb. dancing\r\nc. swimming\r\nd. reading\r\nmolluan to the river to\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. reading</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>4. Tito ada di perpustakaan, hobinya adalah </p><p>    d. membaca</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>d. reading</p><p>library= perpustakaan.</p><p>Tito is in the library. His hobby is <strong>reading.</strong></p><p>Tito berada di perpustakaan. Hobinya adalah <strong>membaca.</strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p>a, singing= bernyanyi\n</p><p>b. dancing= menari\n</p><p>c. swimming= berenang</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terjemahkan-dengan-menggunakan-tenses-yang-tepat-a-andi-memberi-847",
            "question": "Terjemahkan dengan menggunakan tenses yang tepat    A. Andi memberi makan kucingnya 3 hari yang lalu sebelum kucingnya hilang\r\nB. Jill telah mengemudi selaman enam tahun\r\nC. Sam tidak menghadiri kelas matematika kemarin\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>J</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>w</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>b</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>:</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappeared</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappearedB. Jill has been driving for six years</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappearedB. Jill has been driving for six yearsC. Sam didn&#039;t attend math class yesterday</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "a-whats-wrong-with-your-sister-b-she-got-influenza-986",
            "question": "A : whats wrong with your sister\r\n B : she ... got influenza",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>She has got influenza</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1buatlah-ceramah-binggris-tentang-palestina-copas-ngasalgo-782",
            "question": "1.buatlah ceramah b.inggris tentang palestina?    ( copas /ngasal/google /bahasa alien/mars sorry auto report )!!!\r\n#save falestina \r\n#free falestina \r\n#pray for falestina \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Yerusalem or Palestine is the place of the presence of the three heavenly religions. The sound of the call to prayer from the minarets, the sound of church bells, and Hebrew chants from the synagogue, often sounded together.</p><p>   Palestine, for Palestine we pray shortly after praying for personal reasons. Don&#039;t underestimate the Palestinian state, they survive on their land. not for their personal survival but, for Islam too .. because the Aqsa mosque stands majestically there.</p><p></p><p>I have remembered, someone asked one of them \"why are you staying in Palestine? why don&#039;t you go?\" then they (the Palestinians) replied,\"We are still living in Palestine on behalf of the Muslims. If not us, who will protect us?\"</p><p> </p><p>Everyone knows that Palestine is one of the holiest places for Muslims, Christians and Jews.</p><p>There is the Al-Aqsa Mosque, the Holy Church of the Holy Sepulcher, and the Wailing Wall. From these places, the name of the Great and One God was echoed in various languages and dialeg.</p><p>so, if we humans try to help in any way, pray, help services or funds. remind them that they are not alone.</p><p></p><p>yarussalem atau Palestina.</p><p> adalah tempat hadirnya tiga agama langit. Suara azan dari menara masjid, bunyi lonceng gereja, dan kidung-kidung Ibrani dari sinagoge, acap terdengar bersamaan.</p><p> untuk Palestina kami berdoa sesaat setelah berdoa untuk alasan pribadi. Jangan meremehkan negara Palestina, mereka bertahan di tanah mereka. bukan untuk kelangsungan hidup pribadi mereka tetapi, untuk Islam juga.Jangan meremehkan negara Palestina, mereka bertahan di tanah mereka. bukan untuk kelangsungan hidup pribadi mereka tapi, untuk Islam juga.. karena masjid Aqsa berdiri megah disana.</p><p></p><p>aku ingat, seseorang bertanya kepada salah satu dari mereka \"kenapa kamu tinggal di palestina? kenapa kamu tidak pergi?\" kemudian mereka (orang-orang Palestina) menjawab, \u201cKami masih hidup di Palestina atas nama umat Islam. Jika bukan kami, siapa yang akan melindungi?</p><p></p><p>Semua orang tahu bahwa Palestina adalah salah satu tempat paling suci bagi umat Islam, Kristen, dan Yahudi.</p><p>Ada Masjid Al-Aqsa, Gereja Suci Makam Suci, dan Tembok Ratapan.Dari tempat-tempat tersebut, nama Tuhan Yang Maha Esa dikumandangkan dalam berbagai bahasa dan dialeg.</p><p></p><p>jadi, jika kita manusia berusaha lah membantu dengan cara apapun, berdoa, membantu jasa ataupun dana. ingatkan mereka bahwa mereka tidak sendiri</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-invictus-is-a-latin-word-means-a-conquered-b-unconquered-560",
            "question": "5. Invictus is a latin word means ....    a conquered\r\nb. unconquered\r\nc.frightened\r\nd. soul\r\ne. tears\r\n\r\n6. The poem is written by...\r\na.Mariah Carey\r\nb. Pete Seagar\r\nc. William Ernest Hanley\r\nd. Michael Jackso\r\ne.Langston Hughes\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>5.D soul</p><p></p><p>maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "30-what-is-his-birthday-commemorated-for-379",
            "question": "30. What is his birthday commemorated for?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>ghAniA thanks for coming aisyah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>untuk merayakannya bersama keluarga, juga untuk menyambut umur kita yang baru</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Ini jawabannya</p><p>Terima Kasih...</p><p>Maap klo salah, klo benar kasih jawaban tercerdas ya :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "minta-tolong-yg-bisa-di-bantu-yaa-jangan-lupa-sertakan-cara-n-168",
            "question": "Minta tolong.. yg bisa di bantu yaa.. jangan lupa sertakan cara nya.. terimakasih( \u2579\u25bd\u2579 )\u200b.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Apa yang mau dibantu?  Soal aja gk ada :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-arti-mom-l-barowed-your-cluctch-bag-the-one-with-black-suede-539",
            "question": "apa arti mom l barowed your cluctch bag, the one with black suede colour and two side pockets l need it for bima' s birtday party tonight\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>ibu l barow tas cluctch Anda, yang dengan warna suede hitam dan dua saku samping saya membutuhkannya untuk pesta ulang tahun bima malam ini</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>Ibu saya \u00a0mau pinjam dompet tanganmu, yang memiliki sisi warna hitam dan 2 saku samping, aku butuh itu untuk pesta ulang tahun bima malam ini.</p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Selamat Belajar :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "4-the-best-arrangement-of-these-jumbled-sentences-to-be-a-good-r-109",
            "question": "4. The best arrangement of these jumbled sentences to be a good recount text is....    a. Finally I went home with my friends happily.\r\nb.After swimming, I put on again my bathing suit and go to the bathroom to rinse my body.\r\nc. Yesterday I went to swimming pool with my friends.\r\nd.I brought my bag which is full of things I needed in the swimming pool.\r\ne.I wore my clothes and put all the wet clothes into the plastic bag, so my bag would not get wet by water.\r\nf. When we arrived there, I changed my clothes into swimsuit then I did a little warming up before I got into the pool.\r\nA. C-d-f-e-b-a\r\nB. a-c-b-d-f-e\r\nC. d-c-b-f-a-e-\r\nD. b-d-a-f-e-\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>c-d-f-b-e-a</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: i can&#039;t find any correct answer from the option. so, i make one of mine. hope this find you helpful ^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}